<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on karlduino</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on karlduino</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>The text in this work is licensed under CC-BY-4.0, https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/legalcode; code licensed under the MIT license</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>co2 monitor that logs data to google sheets</title>
      <link>/2022/09/26/co2-logged-to-google-sheets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/26/co2-logged-to-google-sheets/</guid>
      <description>In my last post, I went through the details of the (surprisingly easy) process of getting the enterprise wifi eduroam to work on an ESP32 board, as well as logging data to a web-based google spreadsheet using a google form.
I&amp;rsquo;ve now adapted my CO2 monitors to automatically log their data to google sheets. I can swap out the Arduino Nano Every for an ESP32 board that costs half as much ($5 rather than $10), and everything just worked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eduroam wifi and google forms with an ESP32</title>
      <link>/2022/09/23/wifi-eduroam-google-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/23/wifi-eduroam-google-forms/</guid>
      <description>I was excited by our initial success at a low-cost carbon dioxide monitor, so much so that I was immediately thinking about how to scale things up, and how to get more data and in a less cumbersome way.
Our initial build just has a CO2 sensor, a simple Arduino microcontroller, and an LCD display. It shows the current CO2 concentration plus the maximum and average since it was last turned on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>co2 monitors</title>
      <link>/2022/09/22/co2-monitors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/22/co2-monitors/</guid>
      <description>My latest project is a low-cost carbon dioxide monitor.
Many workers at UW-Madison have been concerned about air quality on campus. The university has not been forthcoming about what effort they have devoted to assessing and improving air quality in campus classrooms, meeting rooms, and workspaces. (UW-Madison Facilities has an FAQ on HVAC that is shockingly offensive, even to a completely jaded employee.) And with the removal of the campus mask mandate at spring break last March, mask-wearing on campus has become a rarity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>projects page</title>
      <link>/2022/09/06/projects-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/06/projects-page/</guid>
      <description>I added a projects page, pointing to my current and a few of my old projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new website</title>
      <link>/2022/09/04/new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/09/04/new-website/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on a new project (a low-cost CO2 monitor), which inspired me to create a new website.
My old website is now pretty old (last post 2014-01-14), and I just don&amp;rsquo;t want to touch Wordpress anymore.
But I feel inspired to get back into it, so why not start fresh?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
